[
    {
        "Question": "dual",
        "Answer": "double",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "duplicated",
        "Answer": "copied",
        "Options": "repeated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "durable",
        "Answer": "long lasting",
        "Options": "existing for a long time without significant damage"
    },
    {
        "Question": "duration",
        "Answer": "length of time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dwellers",
        "Answer": "inhabitants",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dwelling",
        "Answer": "living",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dynamic",
        "Answer": "active",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "earn",
        "Answer": "acquire",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ease",
        "Answer": "facilitate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eccentric",
        "Answer": "strange",
        "Options": "erratic"
    },
    {
        "Question": "edible",
        "Answer": "eatable",
        "Options": "things that can be eaten"
    },
    {
        "Question": "efface",
        "Answer": "eliminate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "efficacy",
        "Answer": "effectiveness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "efforts",
        "Answer": "attempts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "elaborate",
        "Answer": "detailed",
        "Options": "complex"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elaborately",
        "Answer": "with great detail",
        "Options": "well develop/ development"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elapsed",
        "Answer": "passed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "elevate",
        "Answer": "raise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eliminate",
        "Answer": "get rid of",
        "Options": "remove"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elite",
        "Answer": "excellent person",
        "Options": "upper class"
    },
    {
        "Question": "elusive",
        "Answer": "difficult to catch",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "elongate",
        "Answer": "stretch",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emante",
        "Answer": "emerge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "embark on",
        "Answer": "start",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "embed",
        "Answer": "enclose",
        "Options": "insert"
    },
    {
        "Question": "embellishing",
        "Answer": "making more attractive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "embody",
        "Answer": "incarnate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emergence",
        "Answer": "rise",
        "Options": "appearance"
    },
    {
        "Question": "emergency",
        "Answer": "crisis",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emergent",
        "Answer": "developing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emitted",
        "Answer": "released",
        "Options": "send out"
    },
    {
        "Question": "empirical",
        "Answer": "based on observation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "employ",
        "Answer": "use",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enabling",
        "Answer": "allowing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enactment",
        "Answer": "performance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "encompasses",
        "Answer": "includes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "encounters",
        "Answer": "meets",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "encourage",
        "Answer": "stimulate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "end",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endangered",
        "Answer": "not abundant",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endeavors",
        "Answer": "efforts",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endorse",
        "Answer": "support",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "endowing",
        "Answer": "providing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enduring",
        "Answer": "lasting",
        "Options": "withstanding"
    },
    {
        "Question": "engage in",
        "Answer": "involve in",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "engraved",
        "Answer": "carved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "engulf",
        "Answer": "swallow",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enhanced",
        "Answer": "improved",
        "Options": "increased"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enlist",
        "Answer": "assist",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enigmatic",
        "Answer": "mysterious",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enjoy",
        "Answer": "experience",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enormous",
        "Answer": "huge",
        "Options": "very large"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enrich",
        "Answer": "enhance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensue",
        "Answer": "result",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensuing",
        "Answer": "subsequent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensure",
        "Answer": "guarantee",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entail",
        "Answer": "involve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enthusiasitc",
        "Answer": "eager",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entirely",
        "Answer": "completely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entitled to",
        "Answer": "give the right to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "environment",
        "Answer": "setting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "envision",
        "Answer": "imagine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ephemeral",
        "Answer": "short-lived",
        "Options": "transient"
    },
    {
        "Question": "episodes",
        "Answer": "occurrence",
        "Options": "a series of events"
    },
    {
        "Question": "epitomize",
        "Answer": "exemplify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "equilibrium",
        "Answer": "balance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "era",
        "Answer": "period",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eradicate",
        "Answer": "remove completely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "erected",
        "Answer": "built/ construct",
        "Options": "stand up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "eroded",
        "Answer": "worn down",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "erratic",
        "Answer": "unpredictable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "erroneous",
        "Answer": "wrong",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "escalated",
        "Answer": "intensified",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "essential",
        "Answer": "fundamental",
        "Options": "integral"
    },
    {
        "Question": "established",
        "Answer": "qualified",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "establishment",
        "Answer": "formation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "estimate",
        "Answer": "projection",
        "Options": "evaluate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ethic",
        "Answer": "set of moral principles",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exaggerate",
        "Answer": "overstate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "excavated",
        "Answer": "dug from the groud",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceed",
        "Answer": "go beyond",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceedingly",
        "Answer": "highly",
        "Options": "extremely"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceptional",
        "Answer": "extraordinary",
        "Options": "unusual"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exclusively",
        "Answer": "solely",
        "Options": "only"
    },
    {
        "Question": "excrete",
        "Answer": "expel",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "execute",
        "Answer": "perform",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exercised",
        "Answer": "applied",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exert",
        "Answer": "utilize",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exhausting",
        "Answer": "extremely tiring",
        "Options": "use up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exhibit",
        "Answer": "display",
        "Options": "show"
    },
    {
        "Question": "expanded",
        "Answer": "was enlarged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "expanse",
        "Answer": "area",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "expansive",
        "Answer": "large",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "expediency",
        "Answer": "advantage",
        "Options": "convenience"
    },
    {
        "Question": "experimental",
        "Answer": "trial",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "explicit",
        "Answer": "obvious",
        "Options": "clear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exploit",
        "Answer": "use to advantage/ taking advantage of",
        "Options": "utilize"
    },
    {
        "Question": "explore",
        "Answer": "investigate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exposed",
        "Answer": "unprotected",
        "Options": "visible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "express",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    }
]